Guide to the Edwin and Terry Murray Comic Book Collection
Edwin and Terry Murray Comic Book Collection
- Assorted Small Publishers
  - Publisher: Dell (Box 355)
    - Title from indicia: John Paul Jones, Issues from: 1950s
    - Title from indicia: Jungle Jim, Issues from: 1950s
    - Title from indicia: Jungle Tales of Tarzan, Issues from: 1960s
    - Title from indicia: King of Kings, Issues from: 1960s
    - Title from indicia: King Richard and the Crusaders, Issues from: 1950s
    - Title from indicia: King of the Royal Mounted, Issues from: 1950s
    - Title from indicia: Knights of the Round Table, Issues from: 1960s
    - Title from indicia: Kona, Issues From: 1960s
    - Title from indicia: The Land Unknown, Issues from: 1950s (Box 359)
    - Title from indicia: Laramie, Issues from: 1960s
    - Title from indicia: Lassie, Issues from: 1950s
    - Title from indicia: The Last Hunt, Issues from: 1950s
    - Title from indicia: Leave it to Beaver, Issues from: 1960s
    - Title from indicia: The Lennon Sisters Life Story, Issues from: 1950s
    - Title from indicia: Life Stories of American Presidents, Issues from: 1950s
    - Title from indicia: The Little People, Issues from: 1950s
    - Title from indicia: The Little Rascals, Issues from: 1950s
    - Title from indicia: The Lone Ranger, Issues from: 1940s,1950s,1960s
    - Title from indicia: The Lone Ranger Movie Story, Issues from: 1950s
    - Title from indicia: The Lone Ranger's Famous Horse Hi-Yo Silver, Issues from: 1950s,1960s
    - Title from indicia: The Lone Ranger's Golden West, Issues from: 1950s
    - Title from indicia: The Lone Ranger's Western Treasury, Issues from: 1950s
    - Title from indicia: Looney Tunes, Issues from: 1960s
    - Title from indicia: Looney Tunes and Merrie Melodies Comics, Issues from: 1940s,1950s
    - Title from indicia: The Lost World, Issues from: 1960s
    - Title from indicia: Luke Short's Top Gun, Issues from: 1950s
    - Title from indicia: Marge's Little Lulu, Issues from: 1940s,1950s
    - Title from indicia: Marge's Little Lulu, Issues from: 1950s,1960s (Box 360)
    - Title from indicia: Marge's Little Lulu and Alvin Storytelling Time, Issues from: 1950s
    - Title from indicia: Marge's Little Lulu on Vacation, Issues from: 1950s
    - Title from indicia: Marge's Little Lulu and her Special Friends, Issues from: 1950s
    - Title from indicia: Marge's Little Lulu and Tubby in Alaska, Issues from: 1950s
    - Title from indicia: Marge's Little Lulu Tubby Annual 1953, Issues from: 1950s
    - Title from indicia: Marge's Little Lulu Tubby Annual 1954, Issues from: 1950s
    - Title from indicia: Marge's Little Lulu and Tubby in Australia, Issues from: 1960s
    - Title from indicia: Marge's Little Lulu and Tubby in Halloween Fun, Issues from: 1950s
    - Title from indicia: Marge's Little Lulu and Tubby in Hawaii, Issues from: 1960s
    - Title from indicia: Marge's Little Lulu and Tubby at Summer Camp, Issues from: 1950s
    - Title from indicia: Marge's Little Lulu and Witch Hazel Halloween Fun, Issues from:1960s
    - Title from indicia: Marge's Tubby and his Clubhouse Pals, Issues from: 1950s
    - Title from indicia: The Mark of Zorro, Issues from: 1940s
    - Title from indicia: The Mask of Zorro, Issues from: 1950s
    - Title from indicia: Maverick, Issues from: 1950s,1960s
    - Title from indicia: Max Brand's Silvertip, Issues from: 1950s
    - Title from indicia: Melvin Monster, Issues from: 1960s
    - Title from indicia: Men Into Space, Issues from: 1960s (Box 361)
    - Title from indicia: M.G.M.'s Mouse Musketeers, Issues from: 1950s,1960s
    - Title from indicia: M.G.M.'s Spike and Tyke, Issues from: 1950s,1960s
    - Title from indicia: M.G.M.'s Tom and Jerry Picnic Time, Issues from: 1950s
    - Title from indicia: M.G.M.'s Tom and Jerry's Summer Fun, Issues from: 1950s
    - Title from indicia: M.G.M.'s Tom and Jerry's Toy Fair, Issues from: 1950s
    - Title from indicia: M.G.M.'s Tom and Jerry's Winter Fun, Issues from: 1950s
    - Title from indicia: M.G.M.'s The Two Mouseketeers, Issues from: 1950s
    - Title from indicia: Mickey Mouse, Issues from: 1940s
    - Title from indicia: Milton Caniff's Steve Canyon, Issues from: 1950s
    - Title from indicia: Mister Ed, the Talking Horse, Issues from: 1960s
    - Title from indicia: Moby Dick, Issues from: 1950s
    - Title from indicia: Moon Mullins, Issues from: 1930s
    - Title from indicia: The Mummy, Issues from: 1960s
    - Title from indicia: Naza, Issues From: 1960s
    - Title from indicia: Neutro, Issues from: 1960s
    - Title from indicia: North to Alaska, Issues from: 1960s
    - Title from indicia: Nukla, Issues from: 1960s
    - Title from indicia: On Stage, Issues from: 1960s
    - Title from indicia: Our Gang Comics, Issues from: 1940s
    - Title from indicia: Peter Gunn, Issues from: 1960s
    - Title from indicia: Petunia, Issues from: 1950s
    - Title from indicia: The Phantom Planet, Issues from: 1960s
    - Title from indicia: Pixie and Dixie and Mr. Jinks, Issues from: 1960s
    - Title from indicia: Pogo Parade, Issues from: 1950s
    - Title from indicia: Pogo Possum, Issues from: 1950s
    - Title from indicia: Popeye, Issues from: 1950s,1960s
    - Title from indicia: Porkey Pig, Issues from: 1940s,1950s,1960s
    - Title from indicia: The Pride and the Passion, Issues from: 1950s
    - Title from indicia: Prince Valiant, Issues from: 1950s
    - Title from indicia: Priscilla's Pop, Issues from: 1950s
    - Title from indicia: Queen of the West Dale Evans, Issues from: 1950s (Box 362)
    - Title from indicia: Quentin Darwood, Issues from: 1950s
    - Title from indicia: The Quest for Zorro, Issues from: 1950s
    - Title from indicia: Quick Draw McGraw, Issues from: 1960s
    - Title from indicia: Rawhide, Issues from: 1950s,1960s
    - Title from indicia: The Real McCoys, Issues from: 1960s
    - Title from indicia: Red Ryder Comics, Issues from: 1940s,1950s
    - Title from indicia: The Return of Zorro, Issues from: 1950s
    - Title from indicia: Rex Allen, Issues from: 1950s
    - Title from indicia: Rickey Nelson, Issues from: 1950s
    - Title from indicia: Rin Tin Tin, Issues from: 1950s
    - Title from indicia: Rin Tin Tin and Rusty, Issues from: 1950s
    - Title from indicia: Rio Bravo, Issues from: 1950s
    - Title from indicia: Rocky and his Friends, Issues from: 1960s
    - Title from indicia: Roy Rogers and Trigger, Issues from: 1950s,1960s
    - Title from indicia: Rudyard Kipling's Mowgli Jungle Book, Issues from: 1950s
    - Title from indicia: Ruff and Reddy, Issues from: 1950s,1960s
    - Title from indicia: Rusty Riley, A Boy, A Horse and A Dog, Issues from: 1950s
    - Title from indicia: Samuel Bronston's El Cid, Issues from: 1960s
    - Title from indicia: Santa Claus Funnies, Issues from: 1950s
    - Title from indicia: Santiago, Issues from: 1950s
    - Title from indicia: Sea Hunt, Issues from: 1950s,1960s
    - Title from indicia: Sergeant Preston of the Yukon, Issues from: 1950s
    - Title from indicia: The Seventh Voyage of Sinbad, Issues from: 1950s
    - Title from indicia: Seventy-Seven Sunset Strip, Issues from: 1960s
    - Title from indicia: Sir Lancelot, Issues from: 1950s
    - Title from indicia: Sir Lancelot and Brian, Issues from: 1950s
    - Title from indicia: Sir Walter Raleigh, Issues from: 1950s
    - Title from indicia: Smilin' Jack, Issues from: 1940s
    - Title from indicia: Smokey the Bear Nature Stories, Issues from: 1960s
    - Title from indicia: Solomon and Sheeba, Issues from: 1950s
    - Title from indicia: Space Man, Issues from: 1960s
    - Title from indicia: Spartacus, Issues from: 1960s
    - Title from indicia: Steve Donovan Western Marshal, Issues from: 1950s
    - Title from indicia: The Story of Ruth, Issues from: 1960s
    - Title from indicia: Sugarfoot, Issues from: 1950s
    - Title from indicia: Super Circus, Issues from: 1950s
    - Title from indicia: Super Comics, Issues from: 1940s
    - Title from indicia: Super Heroes, Issues from: 1960s
    - Title from indicia: The Sword and the Dragon, Issues from: 1960s
    - Title from indicia: The Sword of Zorro, Issues from: 1950s
    - Title from indicia: Tales of the Pony Express, Issues from: 1950s
    - Title from indicia: Tales of Wells Fargo, Issues from: 1950s,1960s
    - Title from indicia: Tarzan, Issues from: 1940s
    - Title from indicia: Terry and the Pirates, Issues from: 1930s
    - Title from indicia: Thief of Baghdad, Issues from: 1960s
    - Title from indicia: Thirteen, Issues from: 1960s
    - Title from indicia: The Three Stooges, Issues from: 1950s
    - Title from indicia: The Three Stooges meet Hercules, Issues from: 1960s
    - Title from indicia: The Three Worlds of Gulliver, Issues from: 1960s
    - Title from indicia: The Time Machine, Issues from: 1960s
    - Title from indicia: Tom Corbett Space Cadet, Issues from: 1950s
    - Title from indicia: Tom and Jerry Winter Carnival, Issues from: 1950s (Box 363)
    - Title from indicia: Tom and Jerry's Back to School, Issues from: 1950s
    - Title from indicia: A Treasury of Dogs, Issues from: 1950s
    - Title from indicia: A Treasury of Horses, Issues from: 1950s
    - Title from indicia: Turok, Son of Stone, Issues from: 1950s,1960s
    - Title from indicia: Tweety and Sylvester, Issues from: 1950s
    - Title from indicia: The Underwater City, Issues from: 1960s
    - Title from indicia: Universal Pictures Presents Dracula-The Mummy and Other Stories, Issues from: 1960s
    - Title from indicia: The Untouchables, Issues from: 1960s
    - Title from indicia: The Valley of Gwangi, Issues from: 1960s
    - Title from indicia: The Vikings, Issues from: 1950s
    - Title from indicia: Voyage to the Bottom of the Sea, Issues from: 1960s
    - Title from indicia: Voyage to the Deep, Issues from: 1960s
    - Title from indicia: Walt Disney's The Absent-Minded Professor, Issues from: 1960s
    - Title from indicia: Walt Disney's Andy Burnett, Issues from: 1950s
    - Title from indicia: Walt Disney's Bear Country, Issues from: 1950s
    - Title from indicia: Walt Disney's Ben and Me, Issues from: 1950s
    - Title from indicia: Walt Disney's Brer Rabbit Does it Again, Issues from: 1940s
    - Title from indicia: Walt Disney's Chip and Dale, Issues from: 1950s
    - Title from indicia: Walt Disney's Christmas in Disneyland, Issues from: 1950s
    - Title from indicia: Walt Disney's Christmas Parade, Issues from: 1940s,1950s
    - Title from indicia: Walt Disney's Clint and Mac, Issues from: 1950s
    - Title from indicia: Walt Disney's Comics and Stories, Issues from: 1940s,1950s
    - Title from indicia: Walt Disney's Comics and Stories, Issues from: 1950s (Box 364)
    - Title from indicia: Walt Disney's Comics and Stories, Issues from: 1950s,1960s (Box 365)
    - Title from indicia: Walt Disney's Covered Wagons Ho!, Issues from: 1950s
    - Title from indicia: Walt Disney's Daisy Duck's Diary, Issues from: 1950s,1960s
    - Title from indicia: Walt Disney's Daisy Duck and Uncle Scrooge Picnic Time, Issues from:1960s
    - Title from indicia: Walt Disney's Daisy Duck and Uncle Scrooge Show Boat, Issues from:1960s
    - Title from indicia: Walt Disney's Darby O'Gill and the Little People, Issues from:1950s
    - Title from indicia: Walt Disney's Davy Crockett at the Alamo, Issues from: 1950s
    - Title from indicia: Walt Disney's Davy Crockett in the Great Keelboat Race, Issues from:1950s
    - Title from indicia: Walt Disney's Davy Crockett, Indian Fighter, Issues from: 1950s
    - Title from indicia: Walt Disney's King of the Wild Frontier, Issues from: 1950s
    - Title from indicia: Walt Disney's Davy Crockett and the River Pirates, Issues from: 1950s
    - Title from indicia: Walt Disney's Disneyland Birthday Party, Issues from: 1950s
    - Title from indicia: Walt Disney's Disneyland U.S.A., Issues from: 1960s
    - Title from indicia: Walt Disney's Donald Duck, Issues from: 1940s,1950s
    - Title from indicia: Walt Disney's Donald Duck, Issues from: 1950s,1960s (Box 366)
    - Title from indicia: Walt Disney's Donald Duck Album, Issues from: 1960s
    - Title from indicia: Walt Disney's Donald Duck Beach Party, Issues from: 1950s
    - Title from indicia: Walt Disney's Donald Duck in Disneyland, Issues from: 1950s
    - Title from indicia: Walt Disney's Donald Duck Fun Book, Issues from: 1950s
    - Title from indicia: Walt Disney's Merry Christmas, Issues from: 1960s
    - Title from indicia: Walt Disney's Donald Duck and Mickey in Disneyland on Tom Sawyer's Island, Issues from: 1950s
    - Title from indicia: Walt Disney's Duck Album, Issues from: 1950s
    - Title from indicia: Walt Disney's Dumbo, Issues from: 1950s
    - Title from indicia: Walt Disney's The First Americans, Issues from: 1950s
    - Title from indicia: Walt Disney's Goofy, Issues from: 1950s,1960s
    - Title from indicia: Walt Disney's The Goofy Adventure Story, Issues from: 1950s
    - Title from indicia: Walt Disney's Grandma Duck's Farm Friends, Issues from: 1950s,1960s
    - Title from indicia: Walt Disney's The Great Family, Issues from: 1950s
    - Title from indicia: Walt Disney's Greyfriars Bobby, Issues from: 1960s
    - Title from indicia: Walt Disney's Gyro Gearloose, Issues from: 1950s,1960s
    - Title from indicia: Walt Disney's The Hardy Boys, Issues from: 1950s
    - Title from indicia: Walt Disney's The Horsemasters, Issues from: 1960s
    - Title from indicia: Walt Disney's Huey, Dewey, and Louie Back to School, Issues from:1950s,1960s
    - Title from indicia: Walt Disney's Jiminey Cricket, Issues from: 1950s
    - Title from indicia: Walt Disney's Jungle Cat, Issues from: 1960s
    - Title from indicia: Walt Disney's Robert Louis Stevenson's Kidnapped, Issues from:1960s
    - Title from indicia: Walt Disney's Lady and the Tramp, Issues from: 1950s
    - Title from indicia: Walt Disney's Lady and the Tramp Album, Issues from: 1950s
    - Title from indicia: Walt Disney's Light in the Forest, Issues from: 1950s
    - Title from indicia: Walt Disney's Lil' Bad Wolf, Issues from: 1950s
    - Title from indicia: Walt Disney's Little Hiawatha, Issues from: 1950s
    - Title from indicia: Walt Disney's Littlest Outlaw, Issues from: 1950s
    - Title from indicia: Walt Disney's Man in Flight, Issues from: 1950s
    - Title from indicia: Walt Disney's Man in Space, Issues from: 1950s
    - Title from indicia: Walt Disney's Mickey and Donald in Vacationland, Issues from:1960s
    - Title from indicia: Walt Disney's Mickey Mouse, Issues from: 1940s,1950s
    - Title from indicia: Walt Disney's Mickey Mouse, Issues from: 1950s,1960s (Box 367)
    - Title from indicia: Walt Disney's Mickey Mouse Album, Issues from: 1960s
    - Title from indicia: Walt Disney's Mickey Mouse Almanac, Issues from: 1950s
    - Title from indicia: Walt Disney's Mickey Mouse Birthday Party, Issues from: 1950s
    - Title from indicia: Walt Disney's Mickey Mouse Club Parade, Issues from: 1950s
    - Title from indicia: Walt Disney's Mickey Mouse in Fantasyland, Issues from: 1950s
    - Title from indicia: Walt Disney's Mickey Mouse in Frontierland, Issues from: 1950s
    - Title from indicia: Walt Disney's Mickey Mouse in Magic Land, Issues from: 1950s
    - Title from indicia: Walt Disney's Mickey Mouse in Summer Fun, Issues from: 1950s
    - Title from indicia: Walt Disney's Moon Pilot, Issues from: 1960s
    - Title from indicia: Walt Disney's The Nature of Things, Issues from: 1950s
    - Title from indicia: Walt Disney's Nikki, Wild Dog of the North, Issues from: 1960s
    - Title from indicia: Walt Disney's Old Yeller, Issues from: 1950s
    - Title from indicia: Walt Disney's Old Ironsides with Johnny Tremain, Issues from: 1950s
    - Title from indicia: Walt Disney's One Hundred One Dalmatians, Issues from: 1960s
    - Title from indicia: Walt Disney's The Parent Trap, Issues from: 1960s
    - Title from indicia: Walt Disney's Paul Revere's Ride with Johnny Tremain, Issues from:1950s
    - Title from indicia: Walt Disney's Perri, Issues from: 1950s
    - Title from indicia: Walt Disney's Peter Pan, Issues from: 1950s
    - Title from indicia: Walt Disney's Peter Pan and Captain Hook, Issues from: 1950s
    - Title from indicia: Walt Disney's Peter Pan Treasure Chest, Issues from: 1950s
    - Title from indicia: Walt Disney's Picnic Party, Issues from: 1950s
    - Title from indicia: Walt Disney's Pluto, Issues from: 1950s
    - Title from indicia: Walt Disney's Pollyanna, Issues from: 1960s
    - Title from indicia: Walt Disney Presents, Issues from: 1960s
      - Cover Title: Walt Disney Presents the Swamp Fox
    - Title from indicia: Walt Disney presents Zorro, Issues from: 1960s
    - Title from indicia: Walt Disney's The Prince and the Pauper, Issues from: 1960s
    - Title from indicia: Walt Disney's Rob Roy, Issues from: 1950s
    - Title from indicia: Walt Disney's Robin Hood, Issues from: 1950s
    - Title from indicia: Walt Disney's Scamp, Issues from: 1950s,1960s
    - Title from indicia: Walt Disney's Secrets of Life, Issues from: 1950s
    - Title from indicia: Walt Disney's Seven Dwarfs, Issues from: 1940s
    - Title from indicia: Walt Disney's Shaggy Dog, Issues from: 1950s
    - Title from indicia: Walt Disney's Silly Symphonies, Issues from: 1950s
    - Title from indicia: Walt Disney's Sleeping Beauty, Issues from: 1950s
    - Title from indicia: Walt Disney's Sleeping Beauty's Fairy Godmothers, Issues from:1950s
    - Title from indicia: Walt Disney's Sleeping Beauty and the Prince, Issues from: 1950s
    - Title from indicia: Walt Disney's Song of the South, Issues from: 1950s
    - Title from indicia: Walt Disney's Spin and Marty, Issues from: 1950s
    - Title from indicia: Walt Disney's Spin and Marty and Annette, Issues from: 1950s
    - Title from indicia: Walt Disney's Stormy, the Thoroughbred with an Inferiority Complex, Issues from: 1950s
    - Title from indicia: Walt Disney's Summer Fun, Issues from: 1950s
    - Title from indicia: Walt Disney's Swiss Family Robinson, Issues from: 1960s
    - Title from indicia: Walt Disney's Ten Who Dared, Issues from: 1960s
    - Title from indicia: Walt Disney's This is Your Life Donald Duck, Issues from: 1960s
    - Title from indicia: Walt Disney's Thumper, Issues from: 1940s
    - Title from indicia: Walt Disney's Toby Tyler, Issues from: 1960s
    - Title from indicia: Walt Disney's Treasure Island, Issues from: 1950s
    - Title from indicia: Walt Disney's True-Life Adventure Beaver Valley, Issues from:1950s
    - Title from indicia: Walt Disney's True-Life Adventure The African Lion, Issues from:1950s
    - Title from indicia: Walt Disney's The Truth About Mother Goose, Issues from: 1950s (Box 368)
    - Title from indicia: Walt Disney's 20,000 Leagues Under the Sea, Issues from: 1950s
    - Title from indicia: Walt Disney's Uncle Donald and his Nephews Dude Ranch, Issues from:1960s
    - Title from indicia: Walt Disney's Uncle Donald and his Nephews Family Fun, Issues from:1960s
    - Title from indicia: Walt Disney's Uncle Scrooge, Issues from: 1950s, 1960s
    - Title from indicia: Walt Disney's Uncle Scrooge goes to Disneyland, Issues from: 1950s
    - Title from indicia: Walt Disney's Vacation in Disneyland, Issues from: 1950s
    - Title from indicia: Walt Disney's Vacation Parade, Issues from: 1950s
    - Title from indicia: Walt Disney's Water Birds and the Olympic Elk, Issues from: 1950s
    - Title from indicia: Walt Disney's White Wilderness, Issues from: 1950s
    - Title from indicia: Walt Disney's The Wonderful Adventures of Pinocchio, Issues from:1950s
    - Title from indicia: Walt Disney's Zorro, Issues from: 1950s, 1960s
    - Title from indicia: Walt Scott's Christmas Stories, Issues from: 1950s
    - Title from indicia: Walter Lantz' New Funnies, Issues from: 1960s
    - Title from indicia: Walter Lantz' T.V. Funnies, Issues from: 1950s
    - Title from indicia: Walter Lantz Woody Woodpecker, Issues from: 1950s, 1960s
    - Title from indicia: Walter Lantz' Woody Woodpecker's Back to School, Issues from:1950s
    - Title from indicia: Walter Lantz' Woody Woodpecker's County Fair, Issues from: 1950s
    - Title from indicia: Walter Lantz' Woody Woodpecker's Family Fun, Issues from: 1950s
    - Title from indicia: Walter Lantz' Woody Woodpecker's Christmas Parade, Issues from:1960s
    - Title from indicia: Walter Lantz' Woody Woodpecker's Christmas Party, Issues from:1960s
    - Title from indicia: Wash Tubbs, Issues from: 1930s (Box 369)
    - Title from indicia: Werewolf, Issues from: 1960s
    - Title from indicia: Western Roundup, Issues from: 1950s
    - Title from indicia: The Wonders of Aladdin, Issues from: 1960s
    - Title from indicia: Wyatt Earp, Issues from: 1950s, 1960s
    - Title from indicia: Yogi Bear Joins the Marines, Issues from: 1960s
    - Title from indicia: Zane Grey's Fighting Caravans, Issues from: 1950s
    - Title from indicia: Zane Grey's Outlaw Trail, Issues from: 1950s
    - Title from indicia: Zane Grey's To the Last Man, Issues from: 1950s
    - Title from indicia: Zoo Parade, Issues from: 1950s
    - Title from indicia: Zulu, Issues From: 1960s
  - Publisher: Deluxe
    - Title from indicia: Wally Wood's T.H.U.N.D.E.R. Agents, Issues from: 1980s
  - Publisher: Disney
    - Title from indicia: Dick Tracy, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Disney's Aladdin: The Official Movie Adaptation, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Disney's Beauty and the Beast, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Disney's Cartoon Tales, Issues from: 1990s
      - Cover Title: Belle and the Beast
    - Title from indicia: Disney's Chip 'n' Dale Rescue Rangers, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Disney's Colossal Comics Collection, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Disney's Comics in 3-D, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Disney's Darkwing Duck Limited Series, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Disney's Ducktales, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Disney's The Little Mermaid, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Disney's The Little Mermaid Limited Series, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Disney's The New Adventures of Beauty and the Beast, Issues from:1990s
    - Title from indicia: Disney's Prince and the Pauper, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Disney's Tale Spin Limited Series: Take Off, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Disney's Tale Spin, Issues from: 1990s (Box 370)
    - Title from indicia: Ducktales: The Movie, Treasure of the Lost Lamp, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Mickey Mouse and Goofy Explore Energy, Issues from: 1970s
    - Title from indicia: Mickey and Goofy Explore Energy Conservation, Issues from: 1970s
    - Title from indicia: The Return of Disney's Aladdin, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: The Rocketeer, The Official Movie Adaptation, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Roger Rabbit, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Roger Rabbit's Toontown, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Shipwrecked!, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Walt Disney's Autumn Adventures, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Walt Disney's Comics and Stories, Issues from: 1940s, 1950s, 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Walt Disney's Donald Duck Adventures, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Walt Disney's Donald Duck Adventures, Issues from: 1990s (Box 371)
    - Title from indicia: Walt Disney's Donald and Scrooge, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Walt Disney's Goofy Adventures, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Walt Disney's Holiday Parade, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Walt Disney's Junior Woodchucks Limited Series, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Walt Disney's The Jungle Book, Issues from: 1990s